

Le Trung Dung

19/12/2002

(+84)842824902

Phuc La, Ha Dong, Ha Noi

Male

■ ekkophantoms123@gmail.com

https://www.facebook.com/dungg.trung .5

Position: Java Developer

SUMMARY

The third year student majoring in Software Engineering at FPT University has experience in Java/JSP/Servlet and basic in React web programming. I look forward to leveraging my skills and knowledge to contribute to the company as a ReactJS Intern.

EDUCATION

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING (SPECIALIZED FIELD: NODEJS -REACTJS)

10/2020 - Present

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI

GPA: 3.08/4

EXPERIENCE

LEADER, DEVELOPER, TESTER

01/2023 - Present

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ONLINE DEBIT BOOK>

- Act as the team leader (team of 5 members) throughout the project
 Successfully designed online debit software allow user can access and CRUD with the debt. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS, JS.
- Manage project progress and divide work, make project reports for members
- · Analyze, test, program and write product reports
- Gitlab: https://gitlab.com/maitranhuy1709/SWP_SE1640_GR3.git

DEVELOPER, TESTER

09/2022 - 11/2022

FPT UNIVERSITY - HA NOI < ATTENDANCE SYSTEM>

- Successfully designed attendance software for lecturers and students allow lecture can check attend to the student. The system use Java Servlet, SQL Server, HTML, CSS
- Project progress management
- · Analyze, test and program, write product reports
- Github: https://github.com/TrungDung1912/IOT1601_PRJ301_ASS.git

ADVANCED SKILL

- English ~ 6.5 IELTS
- · Gitlab/ Github
- · Apache Netbeans IDE 13 / Apache Tomcat 8.5
- · Microsoft SQL Server Management Studio 18

AWARDS

Excellent student of the term: Fall2022

FPT University Scholarship: 70%

BASIC SKILL

- Teamwork
- · Flexible / Adaptable
- · Diligent / Perfectionist / Careful
- Communication

CERTIFICATES

CertNexus Certified Ethical Emerging Technologist

01/2023

Software Development Lifecycle from the University of Minnesota

09/2022

Web Design for Everybody: Basic of Web Development & Coding from University of Michigan

06/2022

Computer Communications from University of Colorado System

01/2022

Academic Skills for University Success from the University of Sydney

09/2021

ACTIVITY

11/2020 - 11/2022 The volunteer of VnExpress Marathon Hanoi Midnight 2020 / 2022

LOGISTICS BOARD F-CAMP FPTU

10/2020 - Present The logistic board of Fcamp 2020 / 2021/ 2022/ 2023

CULTURE BOARD VỊ TẾT FPTU

02/2021 - 03/2021 The culture board of Vị tết 2021